Hello brothers, you know 17 days ago
I had given my Activa for insurance and
today I got a call from them brother, I have
called them so many times in 17 days that you don't even need to
ask brother, sometimes they get
its photos from somewhere, you get the
insurance done, sometimes they are asking for photos from somewhere,
you got the insurance done from there
brother, it is such a hassle I am saying get it
insured, I mean they don't even take five minutes to get the
insurance done and money and
when they care about you brother then
just don't ask, you get bothered by calling,
after 17 days they have given me the scooter, so I got a call
brother, I am going to collect it, only after that you will know
brother, what extra money did
they charge and how has the work been done, have they
put in new parts or is it the same part, have they
repaired it, then how has it been given,
you will know about that only later, so let's go and meet them
directly at the company brother, firstly it is so hot, don't
ask and it is becoming so troublesome to ride the scooter brother, I am
completely exhausted, here you go brother,
finally we have reached, m shr, shall we
go inside  This is the scene, let me take it once,
then I will tell you the whole story brother, how and what all is happening,
I will tell you later, let me take it
once, see this scooty
brother, I had given him the scooty on 6th 65 2024, they
cut off the job that
when you gave him the scooty, get it made
[music] that here is
my scooty brother, this is what has happened brother,
this has changed because earlier he was
writing the idol of Hanuman ji and the name, then that
also got removed from the panel, I will
tell you what is the scene of the panel, Gaurav
brother, get it made friend, I will get this bill made
brother, I don't know, they are charging some amount of Rs. 00, that
file, they are also throwing a lot of tantrums
brother, I had taken them for service first, but
I did not get the service done, they are saying that they will get it done
in an hour, now maybe they have charged, they are saying that the
service will be done in an hour, they are throwing a lot of tantrums, they have made my
mind go crazy,
brother, they are saying that brother, it has
gone a lot  Your scooter is running for Rs. 5000,
but I got this service done earlier,
I think brother,
they did not change it in the previous service, they left the oil as it was,
this strong man is saying that first
eat tobacco and then I will remove it, we are standing there
waiting for him to remove it, brother, take it,
brother, let me tell you the final bill, brother, they
took this 00, they charged you file charges and
brother, after that this is brother, the total
insurance expenses etc. that they have
charged, they have beaten the company up, brother,
look, they have charged labor charges of Rs.
950, the total cost is Rs. 433,
and all these other stuffs etc.,
whatever parts etc. they have installed, they have installed them after spending
thousands of rupees like this,
see brother, these are the works done in your scooter, there is
a cover, handle cover, this one in the
front, they have installed it, it costs
something like Rs. 812 and the rest of the bolts,
adapts etc., they have installed something like this and this  The
denting and painting has been covered brother, it has been removed from here,
they removed the denting and painting
of this area and here where this one is,
both of these had got damaged, so they
removed the denting and painting of these, they have
charged for them, rest brother, in one thing, this
IC is some insurance company, it is a
very bad insurance,
never get it insured from this company, see
here I had told that brother this one is also
in an accident, so their accident was
not counted in the accident, that
company said that brother we will
not give insurance for this and did not give this at all,
rest here also, they left this tent,
now see friend, what a company they are,
what can I say about them, and brother,
I have also got it serviced, so
I had got it serviced, brother, we get the tyre
etc. repaired, this
coil of our scooter is installed in the service and brother, they
put a carbon cleaner after doing something, so I have
put that, the total cost of the service was ₹ 70, if
you got any information from this video, then
brother, like, share,
subscribe,
thank you very much for watching the video brother  Thank you so much
brother, this was it, finally after 17 days he has given
me the scooter, I have travelled a lot for 17 days
brother, I found this scorching heat very
dirty, there is
some company with ICIO board, brother,
I will mention the insurance, that company is
very dirty brother, it is strong in terms of insurance.